What the fuck is he doing?
Come on. I can't wait
out here all day!
All right. Just coming.
I thought you was gonna
leave me out there all day.
I didn't know you were
a removals man. Plank.
Lives and learns. don't ya?
Keep the gates locked now here?
Ya. sorry. Gotta
do business like this now.
Can't be too careful these days.
I know.
Shut it! You say a fucking
word. the right ear goes.
another one - and your left!
- What are you doing. Plank?
- What do you think I'm doing?
Hang on. what are you doing?
Unlock the gate!
Oi! I say unlock the fucking gate!
That's it. Go. go. go!
Fucking move!
What the fuck's going on?
Just hang on. I've got the keys.
The gate's locked! I thought
they weren't gonna...
let the fucking gate locked.
What've you done to Fauntleroy?
I didn't touch him.
He just passed out.
Don't you stand there.
Get the fucking door shut!
D'you want the world to see this?
What's going on down there?
Shit!
Charles. get the rifle out.
We're being fucked.
It must be this one.
Hold that gun. Plank. give me the keys.
Give me the keys. Plank.
Don't point that at my bollocks!
Point it in there!
Planks of wood. I'm working
with fucking planks of wood.
Shit!
What the fuck is that?
- What the fuck's that?
- IT'S ME BREN GUN!
Don't you think you could've
brought something...
a little bit more practical?
Don't none of you slags move.
I'll kill the fucking lot of you!
Who you gonna kill. Plank?
There's no one fuckin' there?
Aaagh! They fucking shot me!
Well. shoot 'em back.
Jesus. Plank! Couldn't you get
smokeless cartridges?
I can't see a bloody thing!
Aaagh! Shit. I've been shot.
I don't fucking believe this.
Could everyone stop getting shot?
John. sit down and patch
yourself up. you tart!
It's a fucking air rifle!
- What the fuck was that?
- Well. that was the bren gun.
You fire that gun again.
you're a dead man.
Understand? Dead!
- No ifs. no buts. you're
a fucking dead man!
All right. all right!
I've got bollock ache with this.
Where's my fucking gun?
All right. Now I've got your attention.
Firstly. I'm gonna blow his toes off.
There go his toes.
Now if you want me out of here.
in five minutes flat.
open the fucking gate
'cause I'm gonna blow his leg off!
They're gonna fucking kill us
if we do. man.
Poor J'll certainly get it
if we don't. He's serious.
I'm losing patience.
Hurry up. girls!
It's all right. all fucking right!
Willie. he doesn't know
you're here.... just...
Sort something out.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
And all your friends.
there's a good lad.
- There's only three of us here.
- I don't believe you.
- Fuck. I'm gonna blow his leg off.
- I mean it. There's only three of us!
- Plank?
- Yeah. one of 'em's out.
Now open the gate.
Up. up. up. there's a good lad.
John. get them tied up.
Plank. where's the money?
There. in those shoe-boxes.
- Where?
- Out the back.
- And the weed?
- Point.
- With what?
- Your fucking hands. now!
- I'm tied up.
Well. nod your head or something!
Check it out.
Plank. get Paul out that van lively.
Knife.
I'm gonna cut him.
Make sure he knows he's dead.
How you doing. Mick?
How d'you think I'm doing?
He's fucking nearly chopped my arm off.
Jesus Christ.
Gordon Bennett.
What the fuck's
been going on here?
Shut up. you idiot.
It's Hanukkah.
Don't just stand there.
Look at the bags. can you fit it all in?
There's a lot... I can't
get Epping Forest in my van.
'Can't'. I don't hear 'can't'.
Bollocks to 'can't'.
You'll fit it all in
if you have to make two trips.
Bollocks!
You got a ticket already. Now if you
don't move it. we will move it for you.
- I'll only be a minute.
- You've already been 15.
- Look. come and have a look.
- At what exactly?
- Well. the van's half full.
- So?
So. all I've got to do
is fill it up. put you in it...
What?
.. and I'm off.
Do you think you can carry
more than one bag this time?
- I can't. My neck. Dog.
- How many more bags?
- Just a couple.
Mick. you dead yet?
I'll be all right. Once I've
dealt with that lanky prick.
Do it quietly.
It's time to say "Goodnight. nurse".
Where the fuck
did she come from?
That is it. Tie her up.
We're out of here.
Not like that.
you idiot. Give it us here.
What you doing. Ed?
D'you want one?
No. I fucking don't.
You cannot make a cup of tea. Edward.
The entire British Empire
was built on cups of tea.
Yeah. and look what happened to that.
And if you think I'm going to war
without one. mate. you're mistaken.
Going to war with what?
Have you forgotten
those guns. you dozy prat?
You won't get away with this.
- Paul. what's that?
- It's a traffic warden.
I can see it's a fuckin' traffic warden.
what's he doing in the back of the van?
He was gonna call the cozzers.
Fair enough -
we'll deal with him later.
How we doing. Tom?
Right as rain.
I'm just gonna take care of the cabs.
Keep us posted.
All right. mate. do you do airports?
Where the hell are we gonna hide?
Don't complicate things.
Just hide.
We're on.
They weigh a pound or two!
Shut up and back up!
Spin round. big boy.
Fuck!
Stay down. Stay down!
Tie 'em up. Tape 'em up.
Hands and face.
On the floor!
Bend over the fucking desk.
Keys. I want keys. now.
I'll find ya.
'Course you will. sweetheart.
What d'you think this is?
Fucking hide-and-seek?
That one. Search that one.
Right. I'll see you in the van.
when you've finished with handsome here.
Jesus. That wasn't
too bad. was it?
When the bottle in my arse has
contracted. I'll let you know.
Bacon. see what we've got.
Let's have a butchers. ey?
We've hit the jackpot. lads.
We've got God knows how much
of this stinking weed.
A shitload of cash.
And a traffic warden.
What?
Jesus. Ed.
We got a traffic warden.
I think he's still alive.
He's got claret
coming out of him somewhere.
What did they want
with a traffic warden?
I don't know.
I don't think we need him.
Knock him out and dump him
at the lights.
Knock him out? What d'you mean.
knock him out? Knock him out with what?
I don't know! Use your imagination.
Don't touch him up.
Knock him out.
I'll knock you out in a minute!
Look. you wanna knock him out.
you knock him out.
I fucking hate traffic wardens.
It's about time you gave my
young friends a visit. Chris.
Tomorrow's the day
and mum's the word.
Now I can't have that.
can I. Baz?
No. Harry. you can't.
I mean it's a liberty.
And I can't have a liberty taken.
can I. Chris?
No. Harry. you can't.
I mean. it's enough
to give me the arsehole.
And I can't have the arsehole.
can I. boys?
No. Harry. you can't.
All right. that's it.
We're done.
We're off.
Here. Ed. are you sure it's a good
idea taking this back to yours?
Why. it's the only place we can take it.
and the last place they're gonna look.
Anyway. fuck it. The battle
is over and the war is won.
Now. Tom. you take this to Nick the
Bubble and we get rid of it quick.
This skunk
is as good as it gets.
All right.
We'll take it. Half price.
I don't think he'll like that.
And you said three five a key.
And... and you know that's a good price.
That was yesterday I
said three and a half.
And now it's today
if I'm not mistaken.
We'll take it tomorrow.
Half price.
If he wants to get rid of it
quick. he'll have to take it.
Now look. I've got a race
coming up in a minute.
so if you'd just be kind enough to...
Lenny.
take that round to Snow White
and the three little chemists.
They should have
a gander of that.
I want a second opinion.
Hang on a minute. Nathan.
something stinks.
Yeah. your fucking aftershave.
Fuck you. funny man.
For God's sake. help me.
I'm in pain.
I'm in so much pain. Jesus!
Go in slowly. Nathan.
Fuck you. funny man.
You go first.
Just get the fuck in there. will you?
I want this house searched for bugs.
l mean I want it stripped.
Where is the point in that? Even if there
was a bug. they'd have taken it with 'em.
It's a bit late
for you to start thinking. John.
If it's a possibility.
that's good enough for me.
I want you to strip this place. I want
every slag this side of Ceylon pulled in.
And tortured... badly.
I want to know
who's responsible for this.
otherwise I'm gonna hold
you all responsible.
Not a bad day.
That pile takes care of Harry.
What's left over?
Give me half a chance
to count it.
What about this gear. then. ey?
Oh. what. you want
a toke on that?
No. I don't think I want any
of that horrible shit.
Can we lock up
and get drunk now. please?
We shot one of them...
in the... er. throat.
What d'you want. a medal?
I'll shoot you in the fuckin throat
if I don't get my ganja back.
The one you shot.
Is he still in there now?
No. it was another one.
That's more like it.
Where is he?
Well. they... they
took him with them.
He's still. still alive.
What did you shoot him with?
An air gun?
Look. we grow weed.
We're not mercenaries.
You don't say.
Who could it be?
Where do we start. Rory?
Mr Breaker.
Today my name is Mr Breaker.
You think this
is a coincidence?
This white shite
steals my things
and thinks that he can
sell it back to me!
He's got less brains
than you. Lenny!
Get Nick - the greasy wop
shistos pezavengy gammore
Greek bastard round here now.
if he's still stupid enough
to be on this planet.
# Come with me.
I'll fill you with desire
# Take my hand and we'll walk
this land together ##
Your stupidity might be
your one saving grace.
Uuh?
Don't uuh me. Greek boy.
How is it your fucking stupid.
soon-to-be-dead friends
thought that they might be able
to steal my cannabis
and then sell it back to me?
Is this a declaration of war?
Is this some white cunt's joke
that black cunts don't get?
'Cause I'm not fucking laughing.
Ni-ko-las!
I know you couldn't
have known my position.
'cause you're not that stupid
that if you did.
you wouldn't have turned up here
scratching your arse.
with that "what's going on here" look
slapped all over your Chevy Chase.
But what you do know
is where these people live.
If you hold back anything.
I'll kill you.
If you bend the truth. or I think
you are bending the truth. I'll kill you.
If you forget anything.
I'll kill you.
In fact. you're gonna have to work
very hard to stay alive. Nick.
Now do you understand
everything I've said?
Because if you don't.
I'll kill you.
Now. Mr Bubble and Squeak...
you may enlighten me.
So we've got a bit
of a problem. don't we?
Er. well... yeah. yeah. we do.
Yea. yeah. we do. In fact.
this is a little bit more...
than looking a bit of a problem. isn't it?
On the scale of things.
you could say it's the
Mount fucking Everest of problems!
And the reason it's such a
mon-fucking-struosity of a problem is...
you don't have the first idea
who did this to us. have you?
Dog. we've... we've been up all night.
It's no one from round here.
We've had 'em all lined up
against the wall.
If it was a toerag
from round the manor. we'd know.
- We'd know.
- You'd know? You'd fucking know?
You wouldn't know if it was
the next door fucking neighbours!
Now get out there and find them!
I'm sick of the fucking sight of you! Get
out of the fucking sight! You look shit!
"Scarface" -
I've watched "Scarface".
If you want to know how to do
a drug deal. you watch "Scarface".
That really inspires confidence.
- This guy. Rory Breaker...
- Rory Breaker?
The psychotic black dwarf with an afro?
That'll be the same man. yes.
I've heard of him -
he's a fucking lunatic.
Well. he can afford to do the deal
at the price we're selling.
It's not worth him
giving us any trouble.
Cause he knows we'll be a pain...
in the arse. And who
needs a pain in the arse?
I'd take a pain in the arse
for half a million quid.
You'd take a pain
in the arse for air miles.
Tom. the fatter you get.
the sadder you get.
Will you two stop flirting
for a minute?
After we pay Hatchet.
this deal puts us up...
nearly 200.000 pounds each.
That's not bad for a morning's work.
l think you'll agree.
So they had the cash.
And the puff.
Cheeky bastards. Count it.
Shit. Dog. There's a lot.
Do you want to do it next door?
We're not going next door
'til we've flayed
them dead men walking.
We'll count it upstairs.
I don't want them to see you fingering the
money when they walk through the door...
Dog. look...
Give it us here... dozy bastard.
Check your guns.
Get yourselves well hid.
You wait till they get right inside
the door. then you give it to'em.
Give me them shooters.
you can use your own.
Yeah.
That's no way
to answer the phone.
Is that you. Dean?
No. it's Lord fucking Lucan.
Who do you think it is?
What can I do for you?
You know those guns I sold you.
l need them back.
Not likely I'm afraid. I don't think
I'll be seeing them again.
Look. I've got the money
to pay for them.
I'm sure you do.
But don't think you understand.
I ain't gonna be seeing them
or the guns again.
We can't get them.
If we can't get them.
we can't get them.
Well. you'll have to fucking get them.
We made a fucking deal for
everything inside the cabinet.
Inside. out-fucking-side -
l don't give a shit.
- You get those guns
because if you don't...
Oh yeah. Bazza. or what?
Have you heard
of Harry Lonsdale?
Otherwise known as "Hack You
Up With an Hatchet Harry"?
Well. this is...
James Bond. need-to-know time.
When you dance with the devil.
you wait for the song to stop.
Know what I mean?
I mean find 'em.
torture 'em and kill 'em.
And bring back
what belongs to me.
Because if you don't.
your family's bang in trouble.
Who was that?
That was Harry Horrible Hatchet.
Jesus. I've heard of him.
Shit. they were
his fucking guns we sold.
We've got to find them.
Now no fucking about now. Nick.
Where can I find those guns?
Six black cocks
and a little white kitten
sitting on the side
of the road.
We're gonna do
a proper decoration job.
I want the grey skies
of London illuminated.
I want that house painted red.
All right. there's this brass
standing on the corner. right?
Dwarf walks up to her
carrying a suitcase...
Winston there
is gonna come along
and see if he recognises
any of them.
Now watch out for these fellas -
They've got a bit of an arsenal
and they don't mind using it.
...and I'm taking down her panties...
Now does everyone here know
what they got to do?
Yeah.
What the fuck is going on?
You got something here
for me. have you?
Come on. chop-chop.
Thank you very much.
- He's got the guns.
Go ahead you get them.
Why me?
You're supposed
to be the hard case...
You go get the guns!
I drive the car!
Good boy.
- Go get the fucking guns.
I'm not going get the fucking
guns! YOU get the fucking guns!
You fucking big...
All right. Wrap them guns up.
Count the money.
Put your seat belt on.
Fucking guns. we've got to get the fucking
guns or we're dead!
.. so I made sure I fucked
the one that was coughing.
Out of the car. you yuppy fucker!
Aaaaaaaagh!
He's the one
we shot in the neck.
Is that right. Mr Botanical?
Jesus!
I don't believe this.
What the fuck has happened here?
Jesus.
The money. The gear.
This is fucked.
No money. No weed.
It's all been replaced
by a pile of corpses.
All right. Don't panic.
Let's think about this.
No. fuck that.
you can think about it.
I'm panicking and I'm off.
How did you get your hands
on these. then?
The boys had 'em.
I know you like
these sort of things -
Wondered if you wanted 'em.
Yeah. I'll have 'em.
- Was it hard getting the money?
- Not especially.
Upset a few characters. though.
Have you counted it?
Yeah. it's all there.
to the pound.
- And they were gonna pay?
- Looks like it.
But who knows?
The opportunity was there.
In my experience it's best
to take that opportunity -
If it's there.
Good work. Chris.
We've got to get those guns.
This is dangerous shit there.
We don't even know who lives there.
Listen. I don't care who lives there!
All's I know is that it's preferable
to death by Hatchet.
Fair enough. Let's go.
I don't think
it's the right move.
It's either that
the old boy's place
and we lose a digit daily.
- I'm gonna phone him.
- As if he'll care.
He'll care. all right? That was
supposed to be his money.
Whether he cares about us
or not. is different.
Pass me the phone.
Yeah? That you. boy?
It's Ed.
if that's what you mean.
'Pay day. ain't it?'
Yeah... I wanted
to talk to you about that.
I'll bet you do.
I got half
a million nicker sitting here.
which means
some poor sod doesn't.
You've been upsetin' a few people. boy.
But that really
isn't my concern. is it?
What does concern me...
is the guns you had.
'l want to talk to you
about that.'
So get your arse over here now.
And I do mean now!
Bastard! You fucking bastard!
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Job well done. We made
a few quid out of that one.
Son...?
Made a few quid. did you?
Where's what I want. now?
You all right down there. mate?
Very fucking funny.
Where's what I want?
I've just left it in the office.
Well. we'd better go to
the office and get it.
that is if you want
your son to see his next birthday.
- Now chop-fucking-chop.
- All right. Fair enough.
Where you going?
It's a thirty second drive
or a five minute walk.
I couldn't have parked outside.
I'd have got a ticket.
I suppose that don't
matter now. does it?
Just be careful.
Right.
You and me.
You and who?
You know where
the door handle is. Tom.
# "The Payback" #
by James Brown
# Pay back
# That's it. pay back.
# Revenge. I'm mad
# Get down with my girlfriend
# That ain't right ##
Oh. no. Not again.
That's it. I'm off.
Tom... that is our bag.
- Ed...!
- Hold on.
This is our bag.
That's it. We're off.
- I'll see you in the car.
I'm gonna take these guns.
Tom. don't fuck about!
- I'll see you in the car. -
Tom! - It'll only take a minute.
What is going on?
I don't know. but what I do know
is there's no more Harry.
Which means
there's no more debt.
And if there's no more debt.
there's no more problem.
And there's no problem with the
neighbours - because they're all dead.
And I think.
if I get this right.
we haven't done anything wrong
and we're in the clear.
Never ever...
has anyone
been as fucking rude...
.. to me...
...as you. YOU... FUCKING... BASTARD!
You all right. mate?
Cheeky bastard!
'Now this was an embarrassing
position for Tom to be in.
'But Chris had to respect
the fact that he was holding
'what appeared to be
a pair of loaded shotguns.
'And Tom had to respect the fact
that they were not loaded.
'So without anybody
losing too much face.
'Tom left through a side door
and Chris left with the money.
'And everybody else got arrested.'
He's not one of 'em.
# Sitting in the cheap seats
underneath the stars
# I'm heading back to base
# I'll drop you off
at mars ##
I think your dad would like
a word with you. Ed.
Where are the others?
They got out yesterday.
They're back at the bar.
# I'm a man machine
# Takin' gasoline
# Super-human being ##
All right. Dad?
I'm all right.
How about yourself?
Could do with a drink. though.
All in good time. All in good time.
So. are you in the clear?
More importantly... am I?
It appears so.
Appears? You'll have to do
better than fucking appears. my friend.
Well. everybody's dead. Dad.
I think that's about as clear
as it can get.
How about that drink?
You know where the bar is.
Eh?
Don't make yourself
too comfortable.
Alan's got to sit there.
Alan!
You're lucky
you're still breathing.
let alone able to walk.
I suggest you take
full advantage of that fact.
# 'Cause I'm a man machine
# Takin' gasoline
# I'm a teen dream
# Super-human being
# I'm a man machine
# I'm a man machine! ##
You took your time.
Where the hell have you been?
Sit down. I'll tell you.
The traffic warden identified
the neighbours' bodies.
Which sort of
puts us in the clear.
The only thing connecting us
with the case...
.. is those shotguns.
And Tom took care of them.
You did take care of the shotguns.
didn't you. Tom?
I wanted to talk to you about that.
Well. talk.
Well. actually... no.
I've got them sittin' in the car.
I.. I was gonna sell 'em
back to Nick the Greek.
but I am having a bit of a problem
gettin' hold of him.
You dippy bastard.
So... the only thing
connecting us with the case
is in the back of your car.
which is parked outside!
They costed 700 quid.
I'm not gonna throw 'em away.
And they're hardly likely to trace
'em back to us. are they?
Do you really think it's worth taking the
the risk for £700?
Tom. you're a dick!
Now you take those guns
and you throw 'em off a bridge.
And throw yourself off while you're at it.
Now... Tom.
- Look. all I'm...
- Now. Tom!
Can I have a beer. please. Dad?
I'm busy. Get it yourself.
It seemed Hatchet
underestimated you lot.
And it seems to have cost him.
I ain't gonna make
the same mistake now. am I?
So I've decided
to bring your bag back.
I think the word you're looking
for. gentlemen. is "thank you".
Thank you.
Now you've presented me
with a problem.
I've lost my employer.
So I've taken care
of meself and me son.
Now if you think that's unfair.
you come and pay me a little visit.
But you better be
waving a white flag.
high and clear
so as I can see it.
Or it'll be the last little visit
you ever make.
You understand?
That's all I've come to say.
There is one more thing...
It's been emotional.
# "Fool's Gold" #
by The Stone Roses
# The gold road's
sure a long road
# Winds on through the hills
for fifteen days ##
We are now officially in...
the money-lending
business. all right. son?
Put your seatbelt on.
We're out of here.
It's empty.
# The pack on my back is aching
# The strap seems
to cut me like a knife
# I'm no clown
l won't back down
# I don't need you
to tell me what's going down...
What's his number?
Don't! Don't! You'll jam the line!
I'll call him!
My fucking batteries!
- No. you muppet!
Give me the phone! Give
me the fucking phone!
- I'll dial it!
- Tell me the number!
- Now give me your phone!
- You'll break it!
- You give me the phone!
- You'll break it and it'll be fucked!
You shut it. It's fucking ringing!
# "Oh Girl" #
by Mauro Pawloski
# I'm eighteen with a bullet
# Got my finger on the trigger
# I'm gonna pull it
# I've picked a clip now
I'm the son of a gun
# So hold it right there.
Little girl. little girl
# We're gonna have big fun
# I may be an oldie
# But I'm a goodie. too
# I'll last forever
# And I'll be good to you
Oh. yes. I will...
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm